[
    {
        "front": "Hashi",
        "back": "Chopsticks",
        "chapter": "Preface"
    },
    {
        "front": "Shinkansen",
        "back": "Bullet Train",
        "chapter": "Preface"
    },
    {
        "front": "Origami",
        "back": "Japanese Paper Folding",
        "chapter": "Preface"
    },
    {
        "front": "Ikebana",
        "back": "Art of Flower Arrangement",
        "chapter": "Preface"
    },
    {
        "front": "Sad≈ç",
        "back": "Japanese Traditional Tea Ceremony",
        "chapter": "Preface"
    },
    {
        "front": "Onsen",
        "back": "Hot Water Bath",
        "chapter": "Preface"
    },
    {
        "front": "Haru",
        "back": "Spring",
        "chapter": "Preface"
    },
    {
        "front": "Natsu",
        "back": "Summer",
        "chapter": "Preface"
    },
    {
        "front": "Aki",
        "back": "Autumn",
        "chapter": "Preface"
    },
    {
        "front": "Fuyu",
        "back": "Winter",
        "chapter": "Preface"
    },
    {
        "front": "Sakura",
        "back": "Cherry Blossom",
        "chapter": "Preface"
    },
    {
        "front": "Momiji",
        "back": "maple, red leaves of autumn",
        "chapter": "Preface"
    },
    {
        "front": "Sushii",
        "back": "(Rice & Fish; Dish)",
        "chapter": "Preface"
    },
    {
        "front": "Sashimi",
        "back": "(Raw Fish; Dish)",
        "chapter": "Preface"
    },
    {
        "front": "Tempura",
        "back": "(Fried Seafood & Vegetables; Dish)",
        "chapter": "Preface"
    },
    {
        "front": "Soba",
        "back": "(Buckwheat Noodles; Dish)",
        "chapter": "Preface"
    }
]